Guide to the Records of The New York Institute for the Humanities RG.37.4
New York University Archives
- Series II. Seminars, Lectures, and Events, 1971-2016; 932.81 Megabytes
  - Auden Festival, 1983; cuid4780 (Box 17, Folder 4-7)
  - Authority Conference, 1977-1978; cuid4784 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - "The Black Lives Matter Effect" Conference -- Poster, April 2016 (Box 97, Folder 18)
  - Roland Barthes Conference, 1983; cuid4785 (Box 17, Folder 9, Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Charles A. Beard Conference, 1981-1982; cuid4786 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Jessica Benjamin Seminar, 1986-1987; cuid4787 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Harry Berger, Jr. Talks on "Fictions of the Pose", September-October 2005
    - Planning Materials, October 2005 (Box 92, Folder 7)
      Materials in box 92, folder 7 are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
    - Poster (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - "Between Hope and History: When Disaster Strikes", March 2010
    - Planning Materials (Box 93, Folder 4)
      Materials in box 93, folder 4 are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
    - Flyer and Press (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Ronald Blythe Lecture, 1979-1980; cuid4788 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Biography Seminar, 1981-1985; cuid4789 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Biography Seminar Budget, undated; cuid4790 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Biography Seminar - Meeting Summaries, 1980-1981; cuid4791 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Biography Seminar Readings, undated; cuid4792 (Box 18, Folder 6-7)
  - Book Parties -- Receptions, 1983; cuid4794 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Jorge Luis Borges Seminar and Lecture, 1982; cuid4795 (Box 18, Folder 9-11)
  - Breyten Breytenbach, 1984; cuid4798 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - "Buggy Love: A Celebration of the Passions of Thomas Eisner", November 2003
    - Program, Correspondence, and Photographs (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Poster (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - "Buggy Redux (The Return of the Bug Man): Thomas Eisner" -- Poster, April-May 2004 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - "Carl Sandburg: Modernist?", April 2007
    - Planning Materials (Box 92, Folder 11)
      Materials in box 92, folder 11 are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
    - Poster (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Censorship Conference, 1980-1981; cuid4799 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Censorship Conference Transcript, 1980; cuid4800 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - City Culture and Urban Design Seminar, 1984 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - "Climate of Concern" Readings and Plays, April 2008
    - Planning Materials (Box 92, Folder 17)
      Materials in box 92, folder 17 are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
    - Poster (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - "Comedies of Fair Use: A Search for Comity in the Intellectual Property Wars" Symposium, April 2006
    - Planning Materials (Box 92, Folder 9)
      Materials in box 92, folder 9 are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
    - Poster (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Commercial Culture Seminar, 1986; cuid4801 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Communism, undated; cuid4802 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Communism and the Intellectual Seminar, 1981; cuid4803 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Conference on Cities in North America (CCNA), 1993-1996
    - Background Materials, 1993-1994 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Planning Materials -- Correspondence, Meeting Minutes, Grant Proposals, and Budgets, 1994-1996 (Box 88, Folder 2-3)
    - Schedules and Programs, 1995 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Speaker Information, 1995 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Papers Delivered, 1995 (Box 88, Folder 6-8)
  - Constructing America, 1985-1987; cuid4805 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Constructing America Readings, 1987-1988; cuid4806 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - "The Critic and the Canon: An Evening in Celebration of Edmund Wilson" -- Planning Materials, October 2007 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Culture and the Actor, 1979-1980; cuid4807 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Culture and the Actor -- Roger Shattuck, 1980; cuid4808 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Culture and Economics, 1984-1986; cuid4809 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Culture of Cities, 1979; cuid4810 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Culture of Cities, 1980; cuid4811 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Culture of Cities, 1981; cuid4812 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Culture of Cities - General, undated; cuid4813 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Natalie Zemon Davis Lecture, 1978-1979; cuid4814 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Daniel Defert Symposium, 1981-1982; cuid4815 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Jacques Derrida "The Law of Genre", 1979; cuid4816 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - "Doing Likewise" Symposium with Jonathan Miller, November 2005
    - Planning Materials (Box 92, Folder 8)
      Materials in box 92, folder 8 are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
    - Poster (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Mary Douglas, undated; cuid4958 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - "Eichmann and Drones", October 2011
    - Planning Materials (Box 93, Folder 11)
      Materials in box 93, folder 11 are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
    - Flyer and Press Release (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - Poster (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - "Ephemera vs. the Apocalypse: Art Spiegelman" -- Poster, September 2004 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - An Evening of Brahms, 1984; cuid4817 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Event Calendars, 1979-1994 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Events -- Programs, Flyers, and Photographs, circa 1976-1980 (Box 87, Folder 4, Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Events -- Contact Sheets, Flyers, and Calendars, 1982-1985 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Events, 1986-1987
    - Calendars, Correspondence, Proposal, and Flyers (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Contact Sheets and Photographs (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Events -- Flyers, Proposal, and Contact Sheets, 1988-1990 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Events, 1991
    - Flyers, Calendar, and Proposal (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Photographs and Contact Sheets (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Events -- Flyers, 1992 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Events, 1993
    - Flyers, Proposal, and Calendars (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - Photographs and Contact Sheets (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Events -- Flyers and Calendars, 1994 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Events -- Correspondence, Calendars, Flyers, Proposal, and Contact Sheets, 1995-1997 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Events -- General -- Flyers, Correspondence, and Contact Sheets, 1998 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Events -- General -- Flyers, Correspondence, and Press, 1999 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Events -- General -- Calendars, Flyers, Biographies, and Correspondence, 2000 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Events -- General -- Calendars, Biographies, Flyers, and Correspondence, 2001 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Events -- General -- Brochure, Flyer, and Program, 2002 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Events -- General -- Brochures and Press, 2003 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Events -- General -- Brochure, Flyer, and Correspondence, January-September 2004 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Events -- General -- Press and Flyers, 2007 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Events -- General -- Press, Flyers, and Postcards, 2008 (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - Events -- General, 2009
    - Planning Materials (Box 93, Folder 3)
      Materials in box 93, folder 3 are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
    - Flyers and Press (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Events -- General, 2010
    - Planning Materials (Box 93, Folder 7)
      Materials in box 93, folder 7 are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
    - Flyers (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Events -- General, 2011
    - Planning Materials (Box 93, Folder 13)
      Materials in box 93, folder 13 are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
    - Flyers (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - Events -- General, 2012
    - Planning Materials (Box 93, Folder 16)
      Materials in box 93, folder 16 are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
    - Flyers (Box 91, Folder 19)
  - Events -- General, 2013
    - Planning Material (Box 93, Folder 20)
      Materials in box 93, folder 20 are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
    - Flyers (Box 91, Folder 23)
  - Exiled Writers Program, 1980; cuid4818 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - "Facing Arbus" -- Poster, February 2004 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - "Far Out: The Sublime Photographic Legacy of the Interplanetary Space Probes" -- Poster, October 2003 (Box Shared University Archives 150, Folder 7)
  - Fellows Lunches, 1980-1988; cuid4819 (Box 20, Folder 9, Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Fellows Lunches -- Speakers, 1993; cuid4820 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Fellows Meetings, 1977-1983; cuid4821 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Fiscal Crisis in New York City, 1981; cuid4822 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Foucault Conference, 1985; cuid4823 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Foucault/Habermas, 1981; cuid4824 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Freedom and Censorship in the Schools, 1981; cuid4825 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Friday Lunch Seminars, 1987-1988; cuid4826 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Michael Fried in Two Lectures on "The Moment of Caravaggio" -- Poster, October 2002 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Future of the Intellectual in New York, 1976; cuid4827 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Gallatin Lectures, 1979-1980; cuid4828 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Gallatin Lectures, 1981; cuid4829 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Gallatin Lectures, 1982; cuid4830 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Gallatin Lectures, 1985; cuid4831 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Gallatin Lectures -- Edmund Leach, 1982-1983; cuid4832 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Gallatin Lectures -- Edward Stankiewicz, 1982-1983; cuid4833 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Gallatin Lectures -- Paul Kiparsky, 1982; cuid4834 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Gallatin Lectures -- New American Music -- Poster, Spring 1982 (Box Shared University Archives 150, Folder 7)
  - Galway Kinnell Readings, undated; cuid4835 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Gemant Lecture on Science and the Humanities, 1990; cuid4836 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Geopolitics of Information -- Anthony Smith, 1980; cuid4837 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Anthony Giddens -- From Marx to Nietzsche?, 1981; cuid4838 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Phillip Glass, 1981-1982; cuid4839 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Phillip Glass -- Gallatin Lecture Transcript, 1982; cuid4840 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - "The Good Old Days: When Christians, Muslims and Jews Got Along" -- Poster, February 2003 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Nadine Gordimer Transcript, 1981; cuid4841 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Jurgen Habermas -- Modernity vs Post-Modernity Transcripts, 1981; cuid4842 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Marilyn Hacker, 1984; cuid4843 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Peter Hanak Lecture, 1982; cuid4844 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - "Hannah Arendt: Right Now", December 2006
    - Planning Materials (Box 92, Folder 10)
      Materials in box 92, folder 10 are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
    - Poster (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - "Harry's Back", October 2010
    - Planning Materials (Box 93, Folder 5)
      Materials in box 93, folder 5 are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
    - Flyer and Press (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Poster (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Hyperbolic Crochet Coral Reef Project, March-May 2008
    - Planning Materials (Box 92, Folder 15)
      Materials in box 92, folder 15 are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
    - Posters (Box 90, Folder 11, Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Photographs, UA_RG_37_4_ER_2
  - Homosexuality Seminar, 1979; cuid4845 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Humanists in Museums Conference, 1982-1986; cuid4846 (Box 22, Folder 2-3)
  - Internal Events, 1983-1987 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Interpretation Seminar, 1985-1986; cuid4849 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Inventing Times Square -- Billboards and Signs, 1988-1989; cuid4848 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Inventing Times Square, 1988-1989; cuid4850 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Inventing Times Square -- Peter Buckley, undated; cuid4851 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Inventing Times Square -- Computer Notes, undated; cuid4852 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Inventing Times Square -- Lewis Erenberg, 1988; cuid4853 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Inventing Times Square -- Richard Fox, 1988; cuid4854 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Inventing Times Square -- Timothy Gilfoyle, undated; cuid4855 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Inventing Times Square -- David C. Hammack, 1988; cuid4856 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Inventing Times Square -- Ada Louise Huxtable, 1988-1989; cuid4857 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Inventing Times Square -- J.B. Jackson, undated; cuid4858 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Inventing Times Square -- Dana C. Kinstler -- Correspondence, 1988-1989; cuid4859 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Inventing Times Square -- Bill Leach, undated; cuid4860 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Inventing Times Square -- Larry May, 1988; cuid4861 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Inventing Times Square -- Brooks McNamara, undated; cuid4862 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Inventing Times Square -- Minda Novek -- Memos, undated; cuid4863 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Inventing Times Square -- Michael Schudson, undated; cuid4864 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Inventing Times Square -- Laurence Senelick, undated; cuid4865 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Inventing Times Square -- Kate Simon, undated; cuid4866 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Inventing Times Square -- Participants' Letters of Response, undated; cuid4867 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Inventing Times Square -- Research Sources, undated; cuid4868 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Inventing Times Square -- Bill Taylor, undated; cuid4869 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Inventing Times Square -- Tobier Papers, undated; cuid4870 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Inventing Times Square -- Joseph Urban, undated; cuid4871 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Inventing Times Square -- Posters, 1988-1989 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - "Iraq and Beyond: A Debate", January 2004
    - Poster (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Photographs Used, UA_RG_37_4_ER_1
      Photographs contain graphic images of human rights violations.
  - Roman Jakobson, undated; cuid4872 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - James Lectures -- Posters, 1979-1980; cuid4873 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - James Lectures, 1980; cuid4874 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - James Lectures, 1981; cuid4875 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - James Lectures -- Invitations, 1982; cuid4876 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - James Lectures, 1983-1984; cuid4877 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - James Lectures, 1984-1985; cuid4878 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - James Lecture -- Borges, Valenzuela, Coleman Transcript, undated; cuid4879 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - James Lecture -- Italo Calvino -- "The Written and Unwritten Word", Spring 1983; cuid4880 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - James Lecture -- Sir Stuart Hampshire -- "History and Conflict", 1983; cuid4881 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - James Lecture -- Francis Haskell -- "Modern Art and its Enemies in the 19th Century", undated; cuid4882 (Box 24, Folder 1-2)
  - James Lecture -- Czeslaw Milosz -- "Conversation on Writing and Politics", 1981; cuid4884 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - James Lecture -- Amartya Sen, 1982; cuid4885 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - James Lecture -- William Weaver -- "Verdi's Taste", 1983; cuid4886 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Japan Conference -- Shitamachi Symposium, undated; cuid4887 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Justin Kaplan -- "The Art of Biography" Transcript, undated; cuid4888 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Ryszard Kapuscinski in Conversation -- Poster, September 2002 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Pavel Kohout "Conversation on Writing and Politics", 1980; cuid4889 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Leszek Kolakowski -- Lecture, 1980; cuid4890 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - George Konrad Reception, undated; cuid4891 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Lacan Conference Programs, undated; cuid4892 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Law and Philosophy Seminar, 1982; cuid4893 (Box 24, Folder 12-13)
  - Law of the Sea Conference, undated; cuid4895 (Box 24, Folder 14, Box 25, Folder 1)
  - "The Legacy of Isaiah Berlin" Conference, October 1998
    - Correspondence and Flyers (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Poster (Flat-file-folder 2 Right)
  - "Library of Dust", April 2009
    - Planning Materials (Box 92, Folder 23)
      Materials in box 92, folder 23 are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
    - Press and Programs (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Poster (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Literature and Censorship, undated; cuid4897 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - "Love and Let Die: Ballooning Longevity, the Quality of Life, and the Coming Generational Smash-Up", June 2013
    - Planning Materials (Box 93, Folder 19)
      Materials in box 93, folder 19 are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
    - Program and Press (Box 91, Folder 22)
    - Poster (Box 97, Folder 16)
  - David Markson Tribute, October 2010
    - Planning Materials (Box 93, Folder 6)
      Materials in box 93, folder 6 are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
    - Press (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Poster (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Marxism and Capitalism, 1981; cuid4898 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Masculinity Seminar, 1984-1985; cuid4899 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Matrix -- Mailing List, 1993-1994; cuid4900 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Yehudi Menuhin -- Lecture, 1984; cuid4901 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Modernisms, undated; cuid4902 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Alberto Moravia -- "Writing and Politics", 1980; cuid4903 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Motherhood and Feminism Seminar, undated; cuid4904 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Mothers and the Avant-Garde, undated; cuid4905 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Narrative Seminar, 1984; cuid4906 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Narrative Seminar, 1985; cuid4907 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Narrative Seminar -- Budget, undated; cuid4908 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - National Humanities Network, 1980-1983 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - New American Music Reception, undated; cuid4909 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - "New Public Intellectuals" -- Poster, March 2016 (Box 97, Folder 17)
  - The New Right Seminar -- Correspondence, undated; cuid4910 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - The New Right Seminar -- Readings, undated; cuid4911 (Box 26, Folder 1-3)
  - NYIH Open House Party, October 1978; cuid4914 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - NYIH Programs Schedules, undated; cuid4921 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Omnivore Journal -- Prototype Issue, August 2003
    - Background Materials, 1978-2001 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Drafts (Box 89, Folder 12-13, Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Images Used (Box 90, Folder 2-3)
    - Proofs (Box 90, Folder 4, Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence and Grant Inquiry, October-November 2004 (Box 92, Folder 4)
      Materials in box 92, folder 4 are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
  - Personal Elements in Professional Authority Seminar -- Barbara Ehrenreich, undated; cuid4915 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Poet's House Events, 1993-1994; cuid4916 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Richard Poirier -- "People, Technology, Literature", undated; cuid4917 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Politics and Theory Proposed Seminar, undated; cuid4918 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Pornography, Obscenity and Freedom -- Bernard Williams, undated; cuid4919 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - "Post Bang: Comics after the the Big Bang!" Symposium, June 2008
    - Planning Materials (Box 92, Folder 18)
      Materials in box 92, folder 18 are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
    - Program (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - Poster and Publication (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - Pre-Modernism, 1982; cuid4920 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - A Program in Comparative Cultural Studies, 1980-1981; cuid4804 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Proof of Names Aryeh Neier, undated; cuid4922 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Psychoanalysis and Sexual Difference (Jessica Benjamin), 1989-1990; cuid4923 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Psychoanalysis and Sexual Difference (Jessica Benjamin), 1990-1991; cuid4924 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Psychoanalysis and Sexual Difference (Jessica Benjamin), 1991-1992; cuid4925 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Psychoanalysis and Sexual Difference (Jessica Benjamin), 1993-1994; cuid4926 (Box 27, Folder 4-5)
  - Public Cultural Policy, undated; cuid4928 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - The Redemption of General Butt Naked Screening, May 2011
    - Planning Materials (Box 93, Folder 9)
      Materials in box 93, folder 9 are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
    - Press (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Steve Reich -- Lecture Transcript 4/21/1982, cuid4929 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Religious Fundamentalism Conference, 1981; cuid4930 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - "Responding to the Art of the Disappeared", March 2007
    - Flyers, Programs, and Press (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Poster (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Romeo and Juliet, November 2008
    - Planning Materials (Box 92, Folder 20)
      Materials in box 92, folder 20 are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
    - Poster (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Oliver Sacks -- Lecture Transcript, undated; cuid4931 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Moshe Safdie Lecture and Exhibit -- Related Materials, undated; cuid4932 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Saskia Sassen-Koob -- New York City Seminar, 1983; cuid4933 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - "Schubert and Solitude: Osvaldo Golijov in Conversation with Fred Child", April 2009
    - Planning Materials (Box 92, Folder 24)
      Materials in box 92, folder 24 are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
    - Programs and Press (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Poster (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Science and the Humanities -- Discussion Transcript, undated; cuid4934 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - The Second Sex -- Thirty Years Later Conference, September 27 - 29, 1979; cuid4978 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    Separated Materials
    This item was found in the case of the 1/4" reel recording (RG37-4_ref2484) of the cSecond Sex-Thirty Years Later Conference during digitization and rehousing and moved to the appropriate location within the Records.
  - "Second Thoughts on the Memory Industry", May 2011
    - Planning Materials (Box 93, Folder 10)
      Materials in box 93, folder 10 are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
    - Program and Press (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Poster (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Seminar on Susan Sontag -- Planning Materials, January-February 2005 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Seminars, 1980-1981; cuid4935 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Seminars, 1986-1991; cuid4936 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Seminars -- Fees, 1990-1991; cuid4937 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Seminars -- General Information, 1994; cuid4938 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Richard Sennett - "The Frog Who Dared to Croak" Reception, undated; cuid4939 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Sexuality, Gender, and Consumerism, 1982-1983; cuid4940 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Sexuality, Gender, and Consumerism, 1984-1985; cuid4941 (Box 28, Folder 9-11)
  - Sexuality, Gender, and Consumerism, 1986-1987; cuid4944 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Sexuality, Gender, and Consumerism, 1987-1988; cuid4945 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Sexuality, Gender, and Consumerism, 1988-1989; cuid4946 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Sexuality, Gender, and Consumerism, 1989-1990; cuid4947 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Sexuality, Gender, and Consumerism, 1990-1991; cuid4948 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Sexuality, Gender, and Consumerism, 1991-1992; cuid4949 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Sexuality and Solitude Michel Foucault and Richard Sennett Seminar, undated; cuid4950 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Sexuality and Solitude Michel Foucault and Richard Sennett Seminar -- Readings, undated; cuid4951 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Sexuality and Solitude Michel Foucault and Richard Sennett -- Transcripts, undated; cuid4952 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - "Sexuality and Terror in Vermeer and After" -- Poster, April 2005 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - "The Shadow, The Mirror, and the Double" -- Ewa Kuryluk, undated; cuid4953 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - "Sheherezade: Fresh Vantages on the 1001 Nights and the Enchantments of Narrative", December 2011
    - Planning Materials (Box 93, Folder 12)
      Materials in box 93, folder 12 are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
    - Poster (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - "Shocked! Shocked! Just How Many Times Can a Country Lose Its Innocence?", October 2007
    - Planning Materials (Box 92, Folder 14)
      Materials in box 92, folder 14 are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
    - Poster (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - "Should You Ever Find Yourself in Solitary: Wry Fancies and Stark Realities", November 2012
    - Planning Materials (Box 93, Folder 15)
      Materials in box 93, folder 15 are closed for 20 years from the latest date.
    - Press and Program (Box 91, Folder 18)
    - Poster (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Stephen Spender Conversation -- Transcript, undated; cuid4954 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Stephen Spender -- "The Poet as 'I' in His Poem", undated; cuid4955 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - "Splendors of Decaying Celluloid" -- Poster, November 2002 (Flat-file-folder 2 Left)
  - Springtime Wonder Cabinet, April 2011
    - Planning Materials (Box 93, Folder 8)